systemsltd.com 2007-08-02

# Systems Limited - Privacy Policy | Pioneer software house of Pakistan offering business solution globally

|   
---  
****  
  
|   
|  | 

_Home_ > Privacy Policy  
  
|  |  |   |  |  |   |   |    
---|---|---|---  
| We at **SL** are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number). That is why **SL** has established this privacy policy, so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information.In general, you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous. **SL** would like to assure you that ** we do not:** | 

|   
  
**Collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us.  
Sell the names and addresses of our customers (site visitors) to outside vendors.   
Support & encourage SPAM emails. ****  
**  
Contacting **Systems Limited**  
If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding **SL** or this website, please contact us: Email: info@systemsltd.com

Mailing Address :

 **PAKISTAN**

**Lahore**  
Chamber of Commerce Building   
11, Sharae Aiwane Tijarat,   
Lahore, Pakistan   
Tel: (+92 42) 6304825, 6304835, 6369390   
Fax: (+92 42) 6368857   
Email: [info@systemsltd.com](mailto:info@systemstld.com.pk)

 **USA**

Visionet Systems Inc.,   
3 Cedar Brook Drive,   
Cranbury, NJ 08512, USA  
Tel: (+1) 609 452-0700   
Fax: (+1) 609 655-5232  
Email:[ info@visionetsystems.com](mailto:info@visionetsystems.com%20)

**Last updated, Dec 29, 2004**  

|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |
